{
    "subject": "resource/Billboard_(magazine)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Billboard (magazine)",
    "human_readable": "The label of Billboard (magazine) is 'Billboard (magazine)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9462502598762512,
            "question": "Is Billboard a magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8579719662666321,
            "question": "What is the label of Billboard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7599552273750305,
            "question": "What type of publication is Billboard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38863036036491394,
            "question": "How often is Billboard published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37973731756210327,
            "question": "Does Billboard have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3387109339237213,
            "question": "What information does Billboard typically cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28609541058540344,
            "question": "Where can you find Billboard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28565558791160583,
            "question": "What makes Billboard unique compared to other publications?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2838585078716278,
            "question": "Has Billboard won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26326194405555725,
            "question": "Who are the target readers of Billboard?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Billboard (magazine) is 'Billboard (magazine)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9177_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Billboard won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9177_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Billboard unique compared to other publications?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9177_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find Billboard?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9177_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9177_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text explicitly states \"Billboard magazine has all that you could want from a publication about today\u2019s music and artists\".  This indicates the label matches. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the label of Billboard (magazine) is indeed 'Billboard (magazine)'. The context provides details about Billboard magazine, including its name, publication history, and characteristics, which all align with the label being 'Billboard (magazine)'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The label of Billboard (magazine) is 'Billboard (magazine)'\" is correct according to the provided documents, as multiple references indicate that the magazine's name is indeed Billboard."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}